<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vegan Pan Dulce UK | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/vegan-pan-dulce-uk/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/vegan-pan-dulce-uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Vegan Pan Dulce UK</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/sharing.png</url><title>Vegan Pan Dulce UK</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/vegan-pan-dulce-uk/</link></image><item><title>Besos</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/besos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/besos/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Two biscuits joined (&lt;em&gt;kissing&lt;/em&gt;) by a layer of strawberry jam, we offer them covered in disecated coconut,
covered in sugar or plain. These delicious biscuits will melt in your mouth!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Cane Syrup, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Fava Beans Preparation, Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded 1-Star Rating of the Great Taste Award!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/24-07-14-palsusto-great-taste-vanilla/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/24-07-14-palsusto-great-taste-vanilla/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We are very happy to announce that our humble &lt;em&gt;Classic Vanilla Concha&lt;/em&gt;, has received a 1-Star rating in the Great Taste Awards!
This is an award earned &lt;strong&gt;solely on taste&lt;/strong&gt;, no branding or company name are presented to the panel of experts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We cannot describe how honoured we feel for this, the product that started everything for us getting such a distinct recognition.
We are extremely grateful to our costumers, who&amp;rsquo;s lovely feedback gave us the confidence to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the &lt;a href="https://gff.co.uk/directory/producer/?id=58543" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Guild of Fine Food&amp;rsquo;s Directory&lt;/a&gt; to
see our product and all the other awardees. Congratulations to all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the specific feedback from the expert judges:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Instantly likeable, with a richness that you would not expect from a vegan food, the sweetness of the product is perfectly balanced, visually appealing, has a very good crumb structure and retains a pleasantly crisp crust. A very enjoyable sweet bread.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;A prettily shaped and well-baked bun, tender and lightly aromatic from the vanilla. The sweet potato has worked well to provide moistness and sweetness, as well as richness in the absence of egg or dairy. We love the gentle crunch of the vanilla sugar. Cleverly executed and easily enjoyable.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Marranitos</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/marranitos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/marranitos/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;These Mexican piggies are a type of pan dulce is reminiscent of gingerbread.
Spiced and sweetened with &lt;strong&gt;Piloncillo&lt;/strong&gt; (unrefined sugar).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’re somewhere between cake and a cookie, not hard but not soft either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Cane Syrup, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Fava Beans Preparation, Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded by Vegan Choice Award (again)!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-10-05-palsusto-vca/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-10-05-palsusto-vca/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We are very happy to announce that two of our new products the iconic &lt;em&gt;Pan de Muerto&lt;/em&gt; and the adorable &lt;em&gt;Marranito&lt;/em&gt;, received this honour!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Louise Jane, CEO of &lt;a href="https://www.veganchoiceawards.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The Vegan Choice Awards&lt;/a&gt;
was kind to share the following words with about our products:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="pan-de-muerto"&gt;Pan de Muerto:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something delectable to help you celebrate the Day of the Dead, Pa&amp;rsquo;l Susto&amp;rsquo;s Vegan Pan de Muerto is hard to beat. This mouthwatering bread will make your taste buds sing!&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s so much more than just a delicious treat. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to connect with Mexican culture, especially when you learn all about the special tradition and history behind this irresistible, zesty, sugar-topped delight.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I loved the taste so much that this product has become a permanent part of my life, and I highly recommend checking this incredible company out if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a sweet connection to the spirit (and otherworldly deliciousness!!!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="marranitos"&gt;Marranitos&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of all of the sweet offerings from Pa’l Susto, and these marranitos are no exception!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like everything else from this brand, these are baked to absolute perfection. They&amp;rsquo;re similar to gingerbread, but even tastier, and they have this incredible texture that&amp;rsquo;s somewhere between cake and a cookie. I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought of pigs as a symbol of luck, so these little piggies are a surefire way to spread good vibes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Forget milk and cookies: Milk and marranitos are the way forward! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t tried them before, these marranitos are really the best you&amp;rsquo;ll find anywhere! And they&amp;rsquo;re completely Vegan!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>