<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Talavera Concha | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/talavera-concha/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/talavera-concha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Talavera Concha</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/sharing.png</url><title>Talavera Concha</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/talavera-concha/</link></image><item><title>Talavera Concha</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/talavera-concha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/talavera-concha/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;These vegan conchas are topped with an detailed pattern similar to the &lt;em&gt;Talavera&lt;/em&gt; tiles found all over Mexico!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be on the lookout for this special pattern to appear!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="please-note"&gt;Please note:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product contains food colouring that may include the colours E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129 - which may have an adverse effect on activity and attention in some children.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>