<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/sharing.png</url><title>Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/</link></image><item><title>Pa'l Susto at the Saint Monday Brewery!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/25-08-24-saint-monday-brewery/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/25-08-24-saint-monday-brewery/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="attention-all-vegans-and-_pan-dulce_-lovers">Attention all vegans and &lt;em>pan dulce&lt;/em> lovers!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We’re joining an incredible Vegan Summer Market with &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lds.kitchen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@lds.kitchen&lt;/a> at @saintmondaybrewery 🍻&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We’re bringing our iconic and award winning conchas, tres leches (including new flavours 👀) and our sweet little cheeky besos 💋&lt;/p>
&lt;p>✨ Expect loads of amazing vegan businesses—don’t miss out!
Come early and grab those treats while they last 💨&lt;/p>
&lt;p>📍 Saint Monday Brewery, E8
📅 Monday 25th August
🕛 12–6pm&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This’ll be our last pop-up before our holiday break…
But don’t worry—the bad boys are coming:
💀 Vegan pan de muerto is getting ready to steal the show again🔥🌼&lt;/p>
&lt;p>🔍 Check out &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lds.kitchen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@lds.kitchen&lt;/a> for more details on the Vegan Summer Market&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pop-up at The Waiting Room Deptford</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/25-08-23-popup-waiting-room/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/25-08-23-popup-waiting-room/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="attention-all-vegans-and-_pan-dulce_-lovers">Attention all vegans and &lt;em>pan dulce&lt;/em> lovers!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Join us at [The Waiting Room Deptford] as we join them for Taco Night!&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Saturday 23rd August 2025&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>We’re bringing the perfect finisher: Mexican desserts including our award winning conchas and the amazing Tres Leches cake like you&amp;rsquo;ve never seen before!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>✨ 1 day only – come through for vegan tres leches cake, the iconic conchas and besos 😘&lt;/p>
&lt;p>📍 The Waiting Room, SE8
📅 Sunday 24th August
🕙 5pm till sell out
🔍 Check their IG profile for more details&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Come by, eat tacos + postres, and have the full experience 🇲🇽
We can’t wait to see you there 🤘&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded 1-Star Rating of the Great Taste Award!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/24-07-14-palsusto-great-taste-vanilla/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/24-07-14-palsusto-great-taste-vanilla/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are very happy to announce that our humble &lt;em>Classic Vanilla Concha&lt;/em>, has received a 1-Star rating in the Great Taste Awards!
This is an award earned &lt;strong>solely on taste&lt;/strong>, no branding or company name are presented to the panel of experts.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We cannot describe how honoured we feel for this, the product that started everything for us getting such a distinct recognition.
We are extremely grateful to our costumers, who&amp;rsquo;s lovely feedback gave us the confidence to apply.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Check the &lt;a href="https://gff.co.uk/directory/producer/?id=58543" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Guild of Fine Food&amp;rsquo;s Directory&lt;/a> to
see our product and all the other awardees. Congratulations to all.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some of the specific feedback from the expert judges:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>&amp;ldquo;Instantly likeable, with a richness that you would not expect from a vegan food, the sweetness of the product is perfectly balanced, visually appealing, has a very good crumb structure and retains a pleasantly crisp crust. A very enjoyable sweet bread.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>&amp;ldquo;A prettily shaped and well-baked bun, tender and lightly aromatic from the vanilla. The sweet potato has worked well to provide moistness and sweetness, as well as richness in the absence of egg or dairy. We love the gentle crunch of the vanilla sugar. Cleverly executed and easily enjoyable.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pa'l Susto at the The Future Market!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/24-07-12-futuremarket-july/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/24-07-12-futuremarket-july/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="attention-all-vegans-and-_pan-dulce_-lovers">Attention all vegans and &lt;em>pan dulce&lt;/em> lovers!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We’re thrilled to be part of the 3-day market with The Future Market in Canopy Market, King’s Cross! 🥳&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Dates &amp;amp; Times:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>✨ Friday 12th July: 12pm - 8pm&lt;/p>
&lt;p>✨ Saturday 13th July: 11am - 6pm&lt;/p>
&lt;p>✨ Sunday 14th July: 11am - 6pm&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Come and support us and other amazing businesses!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And guess what? We’ve got something NEW on the menu that you absolutely don’t want to miss! 🎉 👀
(Yep, fully vegan 😉💚)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>How excited are you? We can’t wait to see you there!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>📣 Share this website with friends and family to come visit &amp;amp; eat some vegan Mexican pan dulce!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pop-up at Black Cat Café</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/23-11-8-popup-black-cat/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/23-11-8-popup-black-cat/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="attention-all-vegans-and-_pan-dulce_-lovers">Attention all vegans and &lt;em>pan dulce&lt;/em> lovers!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Join us at [Black Cat Café] as we prepare for the Day of the Dead in style!&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Sunday, October 8th and 29th&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>There will be traditional Mexican pan dulce, including the iconic Pan de Muerto, flavourful conchas, and adorable Marranitos. Perfect for pairing with your favourite coffee or ssatisfying your sweet tooth after a delightful meal.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Offered all day, so come by anytime to get your hands on these scrumptious treats.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>We are excited to share our unique and delicious vegan pastries with you and look forward to seeing you at Black Cat!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="details-of-special-promotions">Details of special promotions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>We are accepting preorders for collection on those special days.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Otherwise, pop in and get it on the day!&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded by Vegan Choice Award (again)!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-10-05-palsusto-vca/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-10-05-palsusto-vca/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are very happy to announce that two of our new products the iconic &lt;em>Pan de Muerto&lt;/em> and the adorable &lt;em>Marranito&lt;/em>, received this honour!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Louise Jane, CEO of &lt;a href="https://www.veganchoiceawards.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Vegan Choice Awards&lt;/a>
was kind to share the following words with about our products:&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pan-de-muerto">Pan de Muerto:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something delectable to help you celebrate the Day of the Dead, Pa&amp;rsquo;l Susto&amp;rsquo;s Vegan Pan de Muerto is hard to beat. This mouthwatering bread will make your taste buds sing!&lt;/em>
&lt;em>It&amp;rsquo;s so much more than just a delicious treat. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to connect with Mexican culture, especially when you learn all about the special tradition and history behind this irresistible, zesty, sugar-topped delight.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>I loved the taste so much that this product has become a permanent part of my life, and I highly recommend checking this incredible company out if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a sweet connection to the spirit (and otherworldly deliciousness!!!)&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="marranitos">Marranitos&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of all of the sweet offerings from Pa’l Susto, and these marranitos are no exception!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Like everything else from this brand, these are baked to absolute perfection. They&amp;rsquo;re similar to gingerbread, but even tastier, and they have this incredible texture that&amp;rsquo;s somewhere between cake and a cookie. I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought of pigs as a symbol of luck, so these little piggies are a surefire way to spread good vibes.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Forget milk and cookies: Milk and marranitos are the way forward! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t tried them before, these marranitos are really the best you&amp;rsquo;ll find anywhere! And they&amp;rsquo;re completely Vegan!&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pop-up at Westfield Stratford</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/23-04-30-popup-stratford/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/event/23-04-30-popup-stratford/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="attention-all-vegans-and-_pan-dulce_-lovers">Attention all vegans and &lt;em>pan dulce&lt;/em> lovers!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Vegan Pa&amp;rsquo;l Susto is thrilled to announce our first-ever pop-up shop at Westfield Stratford!
Join us on &lt;strong>Sunday, 30th April, 2023&lt;/strong> for a delicious day of vegan conchas and a new treat!
That&amp;rsquo;s right, for the first time ever, you can enjoy our &lt;a href="../../post/23-03-01-palsusto-vca">award winning&lt;/a> conchas directly from us.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>We will be located outside H&amp;amp;M on the Ground Floor.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We have two special promos lined up. First, anyone will be able to pre-order their conchas at the standard price.
And for our beloved customers, we have an exciting opportunity for you to try our newest product,
the &lt;em>marranito&lt;/em>, for free!&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Scroll down to check the details of these promotions.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this chance to indulge in some of the most delicious and unique
mexican vegan pan dulce around.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>We are excited to share our unique and delicious vegan pastries with you and look forward to seeing you at Westfield Stratford!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="details-of-special-promotions">Details of special promotions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>We are offering a special promotion for preorders at our standard prices: £17.70 for 5 and £32.00 for 10 conchas,
which means you can secure your delicious conchas ahead of time and avoid the queue on the day.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Pre-orders close on Wednesday, 26th of April.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Additionally, we have an exclusive offer for our existing customers to taste our newest product, the &lt;em>marranito&lt;/em>,
completely free of charge when purchasing at the popup or via pre-order.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>To qualify for this promotion, you must be a current customer and provide proof of purchase.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded by Vegan Choice Award!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-03-01-palsusto-vca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-03-01-palsusto-vca/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are very happy to announce that both of our classic flavours, vanilla and cacao, received this honour!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Louise Jane, CEO of &lt;a href="https://www.veganchoiceawards.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Vegan Choice Awards&lt;/a>
was kind to share the following words with about our product:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Vegans, rejoice!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>There is now a Mexican home bakery in the UK that makes Vegan Conchas and they are a dream come true! If you&amp;rsquo;ve never tried Conchas, then it&amp;rsquo;s high time you did. And this company makes the best ones around. You can tell that their products are carefully crafted with the greatest of care, resulting in a big difference in quality between their baked goods, and those mass-produced and found in stores. The bread is soft and fluffy, with just the right amount of sweetness and the famous shell topping is baked to absolute perfection.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>They&amp;rsquo;re the perfect anytime treat, but they go especially well with a morning cup of coffee. They make great gifts, too, but once you taste them, you might not want to share! Be sure to follow them on &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/vegan.palsusto" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Instagram&lt;/a> for your chance to get in on the action! You won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss out on Concha Day! Both flavours are a must-try!&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/custom-orders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/custom-orders/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/how-to-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/how-to-order/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/menu/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Gallery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/gallery/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tour</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tour/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tour/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>