<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vegan Mexican Bakery | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/vegan-mexican-bakery/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/vegan-mexican-bakery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Vegan Mexican Bakery</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/sharing.png</url><title>Vegan Mexican Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/vegan-mexican-bakery/</link></image><item><title>Besos</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/besos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/besos/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Two biscuits joined (&lt;em&gt;kissing&lt;/em&gt;) by a layer of strawberry jam, we offer them covered in disecated coconut,
covered in sugar or plain. These delicious biscuits will melt in your mouth!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Cane Syrup, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Fava Beans Preparation, Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cacao</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/cacao/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/cacao/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;These vegan conchas is topped with a cacao sugar shell pattern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Organic Raw Cacao, Fava Beans Preparation, Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Tres Leches</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/tres-leches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/tres-leches/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We are very pleased to bring you the vegan version of this classic mexican cake!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This delicious cake is called &lt;em&gt;tres leches&lt;/em&gt;, which is a sponge cake soaked in three (oat) milks: condensed, evaporated and whole milk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are offering three exquisite flavours: Traditional Strawberry, Chocolate Abuelita, and Delicious Café de Olla!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Soy&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Organic Raw Cacao, Fava Beans Preparation, Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Vanilla</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/vanilla/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/vanilla/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;These vegan conchas are topped with a sugar shell-like pattern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded 1-Star Rating of the Great Taste Award!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/24-07-14-palsusto-great-taste-vanilla/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/24-07-14-palsusto-great-taste-vanilla/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We are very happy to announce that our humble &lt;em&gt;Classic Vanilla Concha&lt;/em&gt;, has received a 1-Star rating in the Great Taste Awards!
This is an award earned &lt;strong&gt;solely on taste&lt;/strong&gt;, no branding or company name are presented to the panel of experts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We cannot describe how honoured we feel for this, the product that started everything for us getting such a distinct recognition.
We are extremely grateful to our costumers, who&amp;rsquo;s lovely feedback gave us the confidence to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the &lt;a href="https://gff.co.uk/directory/producer/?id=58543" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Guild of Fine Food&amp;rsquo;s Directory&lt;/a&gt; to
see our product and all the other awardees. Congratulations to all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the specific feedback from the expert judges:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Instantly likeable, with a richness that you would not expect from a vegan food, the sweetness of the product is perfectly balanced, visually appealing, has a very good crumb structure and retains a pleasantly crisp crust. A very enjoyable sweet bread.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;A prettily shaped and well-baked bun, tender and lightly aromatic from the vanilla. The sweet potato has worked well to provide moistness and sweetness, as well as richness in the absence of egg or dairy. We love the gentle crunch of the vanilla sugar. Cleverly executed and easily enjoyable.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Marranitos</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/marranitos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/marranitos/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;These Mexican piggies are a type of pan dulce is reminiscent of gingerbread.
Spiced and sweetened with &lt;strong&gt;Piloncillo&lt;/strong&gt; (unrefined sugar).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’re somewhere between cake and a cookie, not hard but not soft either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Cane Syrup, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Fava Beans Preparation, Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Pan de Muerto</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/pan-de-muerto/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/pan-de-muerto/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Discover the heart of the &lt;em&gt;Day of the Dead&lt;/em&gt; celebrations with our zesty, symbolic orange flavoured bread.
Traditionally placed on altars to honour and remember loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sold during the months of October/November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Organic Raw Cacao, Fava Beans Preparation, Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded by Vegan Choice Award (again)!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-10-05-palsusto-vca/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-10-05-palsusto-vca/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We are very happy to announce that two of our new products the iconic &lt;em&gt;Pan de Muerto&lt;/em&gt; and the adorable &lt;em&gt;Marranito&lt;/em&gt;, received this honour!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Louise Jane, CEO of &lt;a href="https://www.veganchoiceawards.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The Vegan Choice Awards&lt;/a&gt;
was kind to share the following words with about our products:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="pan-de-muerto"&gt;Pan de Muerto:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something delectable to help you celebrate the Day of the Dead, Pa&amp;rsquo;l Susto&amp;rsquo;s Vegan Pan de Muerto is hard to beat. This mouthwatering bread will make your taste buds sing!&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s so much more than just a delicious treat. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to connect with Mexican culture, especially when you learn all about the special tradition and history behind this irresistible, zesty, sugar-topped delight.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I loved the taste so much that this product has become a permanent part of my life, and I highly recommend checking this incredible company out if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a sweet connection to the spirit (and otherworldly deliciousness!!!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="marranitos"&gt;Marranitos&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of all of the sweet offerings from Pa’l Susto, and these marranitos are no exception!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like everything else from this brand, these are baked to absolute perfection. They&amp;rsquo;re similar to gingerbread, but even tastier, and they have this incredible texture that&amp;rsquo;s somewhere between cake and a cookie. I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought of pigs as a symbol of luck, so these little piggies are a surefire way to spread good vibes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Forget milk and cookies: Milk and marranitos are the way forward! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t tried them before, these marranitos are really the best you&amp;rsquo;ll find anywhere! And they&amp;rsquo;re completely Vegan!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Coloured</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/coloured/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/coloured/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;These vegan conchas are topped with a colourful vanilla sugar shell pattern.
The image shows our &lt;strong&gt;pink&lt;/strong&gt; with a flower pattern, but we make other colours and patterns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We release them on special occasions or when Zaibaa, our baker, is feeling extra creative!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be on the lookout for this special pattern to appear!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="please-note"&gt;Please note:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product contains food colouring that may include the colours E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129 - which may have an adverse effect on activity and attention in some children.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded by Vegan Choice Award!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-03-01-palsusto-vca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-03-01-palsusto-vca/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We are very happy to announce that both of our classic flavours, vanilla and cacao, received this honour!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Louise Jane, CEO of &lt;a href="https://www.veganchoiceawards.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The Vegan Choice Awards&lt;/a&gt;
was kind to share the following words with about our product:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vegans, rejoice!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There is now a Mexican home bakery in the UK that makes Vegan Conchas and they are a dream come true! If you&amp;rsquo;ve never tried Conchas, then it&amp;rsquo;s high time you did. And this company makes the best ones around. You can tell that their products are carefully crafted with the greatest of care, resulting in a big difference in quality between their baked goods, and those mass-produced and found in stores. The bread is soft and fluffy, with just the right amount of sweetness and the famous shell topping is baked to absolute perfection.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re the perfect anytime treat, but they go especially well with a morning cup of coffee. They make great gifts, too, but once you taste them, you might not want to share! Be sure to follow them on &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/vegan.palsusto" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; for your chance to get in on the action! You won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss out on Concha Day! Both flavours are a must-try!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chocoflan</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/chocoflan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/chocoflan/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This delicious cake is called &lt;em&gt;the impossible cake&lt;/em&gt;, it is a chocolate cake cooked on top of a vegan flan
and topped with caramel and walnuts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Organic Raw Cacao, Fava Beans Preparation, Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Koeksisters</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/koeksisters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/koeksisters/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a traditional South African donut from a family recipe. It is a special treat that only comes out on very special occasions.
The donuts are fried, dipped in a spiced sugar syrup, and then spirnkled with coconut flakes. Our bakery is about our family, and
our breads reflect that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for this very special treat!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Organic Raw Cacao, Fava Beans Preparation, Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Noche Buena</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/noche-buena/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/noche-buena/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;For Christmas Day, we created these vegan concha pairs of &lt;em&gt;Noche buena&lt;/em&gt; (Pointsettia) flowers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both Cacao and Vanilla flavours are topped with a detailed pointsettia flower decoration, known as &lt;em&gt;Noche buena&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re sure these designs will pop up again!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="please-note"&gt;Please note:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coloured flower conchas contains food colouring that may include the colours E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129 - which may have an adverse effect on activity and attention in some children.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Rosca de Reyes</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/rosca-de-reyes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/rosca-de-reyes/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This traditional bread for &lt;em&gt;Día de Reyes&lt;/em&gt; (Three Kings&amp;rsquo; Day) is adorned with vibrant candied fruits. It has been remiagined for indivisual sizes and the traditional family sizes to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for this seasonal bread during the months of December/January&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Organic Raw Cacao, Fava Beans Preparation, Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Special Cardamom</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/special-cardamom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/special-cardamom/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;To celebrate the multiethnicity of our family, we created these vegan concha with a cardamom flavour.
We started the concha with a vanilla base and enhanced it with cardamom, then we topped the bread with a
special cardamom and sugar mix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We loved these so much we&amp;rsquo;re thinking of making it a year-round offering!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Spring</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/spring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/spring/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;These vegan conchas are topped with a colourful vanilla sugar shell pattern
and a delicate flower decoration.
We released it on Spring, bringin some colour to our boxes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be on the lookout for this special pattern to appear!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="please-note"&gt;Please note:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product contains food colouring that may include the colours E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129 - which may have an adverse effect on activity and attention in some children.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Strawberry Jam Concha</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/strawberry-jam-concha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/strawberry-jam-concha/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The great vanilla concha filled with delicious strawberry jam!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We loved these so much we&amp;rsquo;re thinking of making it a year-round offering!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>Talavera Concha</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/talavera-concha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/talavera-concha/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;These vegan conchas are topped with an detailed pattern similar to the &lt;em&gt;Talavera&lt;/em&gt; tiles found all over Mexico!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be on the lookout for this special pattern to appear!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="please-note"&gt;Please note:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product contains food colouring that may include the colours E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129 - which may have an adverse effect on activity and attention in some children.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Valentine's Day</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/valentines-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/valentines-day/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;For Valentine&amp;rsquo;s day, we created these vegan concha pairs of hearts and flowers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The cacao flavour was topped with our &lt;a href="../../post/23-03-01-palsusto-vca"&gt;award winning&lt;/a&gt;
cacao topping, but with a heart-shaped pattern.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The vanilla flavour was topped with a pink sugar flower pattern and
a green sugar leaf decoration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re sure these designs will pop up again!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="please-note"&gt;Please note:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coloured flower conchas contains food colouring that may include the colours E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129 - which may have an adverse effect on activity and attention in some children.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>