<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Noche Buena | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/noche-buena/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/noche-buena/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Noche Buena</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/noche-buena/avatar_hue0ee7a6cd23395f2d416729d616cd8dc_2871291_270x270_fill_q75_lanczos_center.jpg</url><title>Noche Buena</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/noche-buena/</link></image></channel></rss>n, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/noche-buena/</guid><description>&lt;p>For Christmas Day, we created these vegan concha pairs of &lt;em>Noche buena&lt;/em> (Pointsettia) flowers&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Both Cacao and Vanilla flavours are topped with a detailed pointsettia flower decoration, known as &lt;em>Noche buena&lt;/em>.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;re sure these designs will pop up again!&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice">Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong>bold&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong>Wheat&lt;/strong> Flour (&lt;strong>Wheat&lt;/strong> Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong>Oat&lt;/strong> Milk (Water, &lt;strong>Oats&lt;/strong>, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong>Wheat&lt;/strong> Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong>Wheat&lt;/strong> Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="please-note">Please note:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The coloured flower conchas contains food colouring that may include the colours E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129 - which may have an adverse effect on activity and attention in some children.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>