<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest News | Pa&#39;l Susto Vegan Bakery</title>
    <link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Latest News</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/icon_hu1e8dee5d716b7cc5cad87f41928086b6_270297_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Latest News</title>
      <link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegan Pa&#39;l Susto Awarded by Vegan Choice Award!</title>
      <link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-03-01-palsusto-vca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-03-01-palsusto-vca/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are very happy to announce that both of our classic flavours, vanilla and cacao, received this honour!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Louise Jane, CEO of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.veganchoiceawards.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;The Vegan Choice Awards&lt;/a&gt;
was kind to share the following words with about our product:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vegans, rejoice!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There is now a Mexican home bakery in the UK that makes Vegan Conchas and they are a dream come true! If you&amp;rsquo;ve never tried Conchas, then it&amp;rsquo;s high time you did. And this company makes the best ones around. You can tell that their products are carefully crafted with the greatest of care, resulting in a big difference in quality between their baked goods, and those mass-produced and found in stores. The bread is soft and fluffy, with just the right amount of sweetness and the famous shell topping is baked to absolute perfection.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re the perfect anytime treat, but they go especially well with a morning cup of coffee. They make great gifts, too, but once you taste them, you might not want to share! Be sure to follow them on &lt;a href=&#34;https://instagram.com/vegan.palsusto&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; for your chance to get in on the action! You won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss out on Concha Day! Both flavours are a must-try!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
