<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rosca De Reyes | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/rosca-de-reyes/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/rosca-de-reyes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Rosca De Reyes</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/sharing.png</url><title>Rosca De Reyes</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/rosca-de-reyes/</link></image><item><title>Rosca de Reyes</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/rosca-de-reyes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/rosca-de-reyes/</guid><description>&lt;p>This traditional bread for &lt;em>Día de Reyes&lt;/em> (Three Kings&amp;rsquo; Day) is adorned with vibrant candied fruits. It has been remiagined for indivisual sizes and the traditional family sizes to share.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Look for this seasonal bread during the months of December/January&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice">Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong>bold&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>INGREDIENTS: &lt;strong>Wheat&lt;/strong> Flour (&lt;strong>Wheat&lt;/strong> Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong>Oat&lt;/strong> Milk (Water, &lt;strong>Oats&lt;/strong>, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong>Wheat&lt;/strong> Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Organic Raw Cacao, Fava Beans Preparation, Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong>Wheat&lt;/strong> Starch.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item></channel></rss>