<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Strawberry Jam Concha | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/strawberry-jam-concha/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/strawberry-jam-concha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Strawberry Jam Concha</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/sharing.png</url><title>Strawberry Jam Concha</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/strawberry-jam-concha/</link></image><item><title>Strawberry Jam Concha</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/strawberry-jam-concha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/strawberry-jam-concha/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The great vanilla concha filled with delicious strawberry jam!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We loved these so much we&amp;rsquo;re thinking of making it a year-round offering!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>