<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pan de Muerto | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/pan-de-muerto/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/pan-de-muerto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Pan de Muerto</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/pan-de-muerto/avatar_hu_31a589a1e7e044ad.png</url><title>Pan de Muerto</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/pan-de-muerto/</link></image><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded by Vegan Choice Award (again)!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-10-05-palsusto-vca/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/23-10-05-palsusto-vca/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We are very happy to announce that two of our new products the iconic &lt;em&gt;Pan de Muerto&lt;/em&gt; and the adorable &lt;em&gt;Marranito&lt;/em&gt;, received this honour!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Louise Jane, CEO of &lt;a href="https://www.veganchoiceawards.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The Vegan Choice Awards&lt;/a&gt;
was kind to share the following words with about our products:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="pan-de-muerto"&gt;Pan de Muerto:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something delectable to help you celebrate the Day of the Dead, Pa&amp;rsquo;l Susto&amp;rsquo;s Vegan Pan de Muerto is hard to beat. This mouthwatering bread will make your taste buds sing!&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s so much more than just a delicious treat. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to connect with Mexican culture, especially when you learn all about the special tradition and history behind this irresistible, zesty, sugar-topped delight.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I loved the taste so much that this product has become a permanent part of my life, and I highly recommend checking this incredible company out if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a sweet connection to the spirit (and otherworldly deliciousness!!!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="marranitos"&gt;Marranitos&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of all of the sweet offerings from Pa’l Susto, and these marranitos are no exception!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like everything else from this brand, these are baked to absolute perfection. They&amp;rsquo;re similar to gingerbread, but even tastier, and they have this incredible texture that&amp;rsquo;s somewhere between cake and a cookie. I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought of pigs as a symbol of luck, so these little piggies are a surefire way to spread good vibes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Forget milk and cookies: Milk and marranitos are the way forward! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t tried them before, these marranitos are really the best you&amp;rsquo;ll find anywhere! And they&amp;rsquo;re completely Vegan!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>