<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Great Taste Award | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/great-taste-award/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/great-taste-award/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Great Taste Award</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/sharing.png</url><title>Great Taste Award</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/tag/great-taste-award/</link></image><item><title>Vegan Pa'l Susto Awarded 1-Star Rating of the Great Taste Award!</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/24-07-14-palsusto-great-taste-vanilla/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/post/24-07-14-palsusto-great-taste-vanilla/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are very happy to announce that our humble &lt;em>Classic Vanilla Concha&lt;/em>, has received a 1-Star rating in the Great Taste Awards!
This is an award earned &lt;strong>solely on taste&lt;/strong>, no branding or company name are presented to the panel of experts.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We cannot describe how honoured we feel for this, the product that started everything for us getting such a distinct recognition.
We are extremely grateful to our costumers, who&amp;rsquo;s lovely feedback gave us the confidence to apply.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Check the &lt;a href="https://gff.co.uk/directory/producer/?id=58543" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Guild of Fine Food&amp;rsquo;s Directory&lt;/a> to
see our product and all the other awardees. Congratulations to all.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some of the specific feedback from the expert judges:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>&amp;ldquo;Instantly likeable, with a richness that you would not expect from a vegan food, the sweetness of the product is perfectly balanced, visually appealing, has a very good crumb structure and retains a pleasantly crisp crust. A very enjoyable sweet bread.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>&amp;ldquo;A prettily shaped and well-baked bun, tender and lightly aromatic from the vanilla. The sweet potato has worked well to provide moistness and sweetness, as well as richness in the absence of egg or dairy. We love the gentle crunch of the vanilla sugar. Cleverly executed and easily enjoyable.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>