<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Special Cardamom | Pa'l Susto Vegan Bakery</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/special-cardamom/</link><atom:link href="https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/special-cardamom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Special Cardamom</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/media/sharing.png</url><title>Special Cardamom</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/special-cardamom/</link></image><item><title>Special Cardamom</title><link>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/special-cardamom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veganpalsusto.co.uk/product/special-cardamom/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;To celebrate the multiethnicity of our family, we created these vegan concha with a cardamom flavour.
We started the concha with a vanilla base and enhanced it with cardamom, then we topped the bread with a
special cardamom and sugar mix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We loved these so much we&amp;rsquo;re thinking of making it a year-round offering!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id="allergen-advice"&gt;Allergen Advice:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For allergens, including cereals containing gluten, see ingredients in &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kitchen handles: gluten, nuts, peanuts, sesame, celery, mustard and soybeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a severe allergy to nuts or any other main allergen, we recommend you not to have our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INGREDIENTS:
&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour (&lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Flour, Calcium Carbonate, Iron, Niacin, Thiamin), &lt;strong&gt;Oat&lt;/strong&gt; Milk (Water, &lt;strong&gt;Oats&lt;/strong&gt;, Anti-caking Agents (Tricalcium Phosphate, Calcium Carbonate), Rapeseed Oil, Salt), Plant Oils (Palm, Sunflower, Rapeseed), Sweet Potato, Sugar, Water, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Gluten, Sea Salt, Dried Yeast, Fava Beans Preparation, Vanilla (Water, Carrier (Propylene Glycol), Flavouring, Colour (Plain Caramel)), Emulsifiers (Sunflower Lecithins, Sorbitan Monostearate), Flavouring, Stabiliser (Calcium Sulphate), Flour Treatment Agents (Ascorbic Acid, Alpha-Amylase), Salt, &lt;strong&gt;Wheat&lt;/strong&gt; Starch, Vegetable Glycerine, Silicone Dioxide, Propylene glycol, Colours: E102, E104, E110, E122, E124 and E129.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>